Yep, he's definitely, exactly who is as he is, Timon!
是的   他绝对   肯定就是他    丁满
So for me the suitcase is definitely his!
所以对我来说   这箱子肯定是他的
Criminal Quint thanks you all for finding his suitcase
罪犯昆汀感谢你们找到了他的箱子
and wishes to give you a reward -- one dollar!
并希望给你们一个奖励 一美元
Gee thanks, sure you can spare it!
天哪   谢谢   确实你可以分配钱
So long, suckers, I mean,
再见了   失败者   我是说
citizens! Hah hah hah hah hah!
公民们   哈哈哈哈哈
Yeah yeah yeah yeah! We got one dollar!
耶耶耶耶   我们得到了一美元
We got one dollar! Yeah yeah yeah yeah!
我们得到了一美元   耶耶耶耶
Wow, yeah, man! We did the right thing now, Timon!
喔   耶   伙计   我们的做法是正确的   丁满
Oh, yes, Pumbaa, I'm very glad we did the right thing.
哦   是的   彭彭   我很开心我们做了正确的事
See my big glad smile! Yeah!
看到我又大又欢乐的笑容了吗   耶